(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-20T23:36:01.856361",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Wait, this is good.
I did it.
I infiltrated this place.
Success! 大成功じゃ！
Success! Total success!
みんなに見られてた！
Everyone saw me!
うわー！
Uwaaa!
I can't believe you guys were watching me this whole time!
No!
To be honest...
I did feel eyes on me, but...
I knew you guys were watching, so it's okay.
Anyways, it's not the time to be talking about that,
because...
Today's a special day for me!
Today is... Do you know what today is?
Say it, say it! Say it, say it!
What is today? Say it!
Yeah, today's my birthday!
Happy birthday Zeta!
Selamat ulang tahun~
Happy birthday to you~
Gitu gak sih lagunya?
Is that how the song goes?
I don't know!
What, you're saying something?
Nope.
Skill... skill... skill issue?!
You're saying I'm a noob as a secret agent?
Bull-- Okay, I can't say the rest.
Bulls!
Bull!
You're lying! You're lying!
That can't be true!
I've been working hard,
I've got the stamina,
and obviously the intelligence,
IQ 200!
And strength, you know?
Look at the power as well, yeah yeah yeah.
So anyways, don't you worry,
because I've got the perfect thing for today!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah!
Have you ever heard of a... of a...
of a secret agent school?
Yeah, so...
Back in my days, back in my days,
I've been through hell and back,
so I invited some transfer students here,
so we can prove that I'm the best secret agent, okay?
So we're gonna do some tests together
to see how tough it is to become
a professional secret agent like me!
Like me, like me, like me! I'm a good example.
Anyways, it reminds me of my...
old 学校 exam, you know?
old school exam, you know?
But to be honest...
To be honest, I don't know what we'll be doing yet, but...
Wait! Oh crap, okay.
It's almost time for the first test!
最初のテストが... そろそろ...
The first test is starting soon...
あ！早く行かないと！ Bye!
Ah! I have to hurry and go! Bye!
助けてー！
Help me!
なんかさ... あれ？
Wait, what's...
ゾンビ？
A zombie?
あれ？なんかみこちのカマキリの威嚇ポーズにビビってる！
Huh? It's scared of Mikochi's praying mantis threat pose!
あ、ビビってる！ビビってる！
Ah, it's scared! It's scared!
これみこちゃん分かりました。コイツ雑魚ゾンビです！
I figured it out. This guy is a weakling zombie!
ざぁ～こ♡
Super weakling~
コイツドMかもしれない！ドMゾンビ！
Maybe he's a total masochist! A masochist zombie!
ポンコツ～！
Clumsy weakling~!
あ、効いてる！みこちゃんも行って？
Ah, it's working! Miko-chan, you try too!
ざぁ～こ♡
Super weakling~
効いてる効いてる！珍しい！
It's working, it's working! How unusual!
ちょっと弱々ゾンビさんなんじゃない？
Isn't he just a super weak zombie?
全然怖くないんですけど！
He's not scary at all!
はーい！みんなー！
Hi, everyone!
あ、ゼータ！
Oh, Zeta!
遅れてごめーん！
Sorry I'm late!
ゼータちゃんだ！遅刻ゾンビ！
It's Zeta-chan! Tardy zombie!
何このゾンビ？
What's with this zombie?
あれは弱々ゾンビだよ。
That's a super weak zombie.
エージェント試験の最初のテストにお招きしたけど...
We invited him for the first test of the agent exam, but...
ゾンビも新入生なのかな？
...is the zombie a freshman too?
えー！？新入生ー？！
What?! A freshman?!
そうだ、でも言葉通じないけどさ、ゾンビに。
Right, but we can't communicate with a zombie.
ゼータは色んな言葉話せるよね？
Zeta, you can speak many languages, right?
ゾンビ語も喋れるんじゃない？
Can't you speak zombie language too?
オッケーオッケー。
Okay, okay.
行けー！
Go!
ちょっと弱そうかも。
He seems a bit weak.
会話してる！
They're having a conversation!
よし！出来た！
Alright! I did it!
おい！ゾンビ！
Oi! Zombie!
何してるの！怖がらせろって言ったでしょ？！
What are you doing?! I told you to be scary, right?!
ほんとうに何やってたのよ？！
What have you been doing?!
ごめんなさいね。どうやら弱っちいゾンビを送っちゃったみたい。
Apologies. I probably sent over the weak zombies.
申し訳ないわね。
Sorry about that.
さて、今日はみなさんにサプライズテストをご用意しました。
Anyways, I called you guys here for a surprise test
シークレットエージェントにふさわしいか、確かめてみましょう。
to see if you guys are fit to be a secret agent.
なんか分かんねぇけど受けてみるか！
I don't really get it, but let me give it a try!
受けてみよう！
Let's take it!
さてさて、みなさん落ち着いてくださいね。
Okay, okay, calm down everyone.
では、この箱の中身を当ててもらうテストになりまーす！
In this test, you will need to guess what is inside the box!
これはあなたたちの推理力が試されますよ。
This requires your investigative skills.
ラウンド1では、30秒間だけ中身に触れられます。
For round 1, you can feel the object for 30 seconds only.
みなさんのリアクション、すごーく楽しみですね！
Can't wait to see your reactions!
いいリアクション期待してるよ、だって！
She says she's expecting good reactions!
完全になめられてるから！
We're totally being underestimated!
じゃあ、AZKi先輩からかな！
Then, should we start with AZKi-senpai?
任せてくださいよ！
Leave it to me!
みんなで協力してさ...
Let's all cooperate on this...
情報を伝えることに集中したいと思います！
I want to focus on sharing information!
AZKiの挑戦
[AZKi's Challenge]
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
はい！えっ、何これ... コードのような...
Okay! Wait, what is this... something like a cord...
何これ？！
What is this?!
え、なんかジタバタしてます！ジタバタ！
Wait, it's thrashing around! Thrashing!
なんか動いてる！
It's moving!
え、何？なんか動いている... けど！
Wait, what? It's moving... but!
Time's up!
フォルムが分からない！
I can't tell its shape!
なんか足がバタバタしてる...
It feels like its legs are flailing...
バタバタ？！えー？！やばい！
Flailing?! What?! Oh no!
大神ミオの挑戦
[Ookami Mio's Challenge]
じゃあ、ミオちゃん！スタート！
Next up, Mio-chan! Start!
おらー！
Oraaa!
怖い怖い怖い...
Scary, scary, scary...
ん？何か... あ！あ、でも分かったかもこれウチ！
Huh? Something... Ah! Ah, but I might have figured it out!
あ〜なるほど！はいはいはい！はいはいはいはい！
Ah, I see! Right, right, right! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
あ〜元気ですね！
Ah, it's so lively!
元気？！怖ーい！
Lively?! Scary!
元気です！完全に生きてますやん！
It's lively! It's totally alive!
あー元気だったなー。すごい元気だった。
Ah, it was so lively. It was super lively.
なんか穏やかな表情...
What a calm expression...
さくらみこの挑戦
[Sakura Miko's Challenge]
ゴッドハンドでやらせていただきます！
I will be doing this with God's hand!
Three, two, one, go!
スタート！
Start!
何かに触れた模様...
Looks like I touched something...
やめろ！
Stop it!
ガチですか？
Are you serious?
ガチなやつ... ガチなやつ...
It's a real one... a real one...
ねぇ、やめて！
Hey, stop it!
真剣な表情...
What a serious expression...
全然わからない！
I have no idea!
終わりだよー！
Time's up!
え？ゴッドハンド？
Huh? God Hand?
こうやってブーッてなって...
It was vibrating like "buzz, buzz"!
じゃあ次はゼタの挑戦！
Next is Zeta's challenge!
ベスティア・ゼタの挑戦
[Title: Bestia Zeta's Challenge]
いきますよー！
Here we go!
3、2、1、スタート！
Three, two, one, start!
飛ぶぞあいつ！
That thing's gonna fly!
え？これ生きてるやん！
Huh? This thing is alive!
いや、多分生きてはいない気はするけど...
Wait, I feel like it's probably not alive, but...
え？何これ？
Huh? What is this?
なんかちゃんと触っています
She's properly touching it.
形を確認しているのでしょうか？
Is she checking its shape?
え？飛んでる？
Huh? Is it flying?
なんか飛びそうではあるよね
It does look like it might jump/fly.
飛びそう？
Might jump?
生きてる...
It's alive...
うわぁー！ちょっと！
Whoa! Hold on!
でもこれみんなでね...
But everyone together...
力を合わせてね
Combining our strength...
なんかプロペラがついたもの...
Something with a propeller attached...
マジでみくの手を入れたときブルルッてなったから
Seriously, when I put my hand in, it went "bzzzz"!
アヒルとかの足がこうパタパタパタってなってるのか...
Or maybe a duck's feet flapping back and forth...
これはズバリ、カエルのおもちゃです！
This is definitely a frog toy!
カエルのおもちゃってこと？
You mean a frog toy?
ゼタちゃん、みんなの回答をまとめよう！
Zeta-chan, let's summarize everyone's answers!
ミオ先輩の答えで！
Let's go with Mio-senpai's answer!
自信満々だったもんね！
She was so confident!
カエルのおもちゃかな！
Maybe a frog toy!
カエルのおもちゃで！
A frog toy, then!
お、よくできました！
Oh, well done!
合ってるー！
It's correct!
すごーい！
Amazing!
何がポイントだったんですか？
What gave it away?
触った感じがピタピタしてて...
The feel was kinda sticky and rubbery...
ピョンピョンしてたから、カエルのおもちゃっぽいなって思って！
And it was hopping around, so I thought it seemed like a frog toy!
すごーい！素晴らしい！
Wow! Amazing!
じゃあ次の問題 お願いします！
Okay, next question please!
じゃあうちがいってみますか！
Shall I go next?
ゴッドハンドミオで行きますか！
Let's go with God Hand Mio!
大神ミオの挑戦
[Title: Ookami Mio's Challenge]
スタート！
Start!
え？何何？怖い怖い！ホラー！
Huh? What is this? Scary! It's horror!
ミオちゃんが怖がっている
Mio-chan is getting scared.
嘘でしょ！？何これ！？怖い！
No way! What is this?! Scary!
何なんだよこれ！気持ち悪い！
What on earth is this?! Gross!
気持ち悪い？
Gross?
何これ！？何これ！？
What is this?! What is this?!
怖い怖い怖い！
Scary, scary, scary!
音じゃないの？その反応...
Isn't that reaction because of a sound?
いやー！いやー！
Nooo! Nooo!
大袈裟にやってるんじゃない？
Aren't you exaggerating?
なんか嫌だ！ちょっと行ってみて！
I hate this! Someone try it, try it!
AZKi行け！AZKi先輩頑張れ！
Go, AZKi! Do your best, AZKi-senpai!
AZKiの挑戦
[Title: AZKi's Challenge]
スタート！
Start!
やっぱそうだよね
I knew it.
え？何？え？何？
Huh? What? What is it?
いや その反応になるって！
See, anyone would react like that!
モシャモシャしてます...
It feels shaggy...
ヒントは？
Any hints?
モシャモシャ...
Shaggy...
なんかベタベタしてて...
It's kind of sticky...
でもこれ多分... 何かのパーツ...
But this is probably... some kind of part...
何かと言われたらむずいんだけど
If you ask "what part", that's tough though...
なんかちょっと心にダメージ受けるよね
This gives you emotional damage, doesn't it?
ゼタ行くか！
Should Zeta go next?!
ベスティア・ゼタの挑戦
[Title: Bestia Zeta's Challenge]
スタート！
Start!
初手 初手驚くよね
At first, at first you're surprised, right?
そう 最初は驚くね これ
Yeah, you get surprised at first with this.
えー？
Eh?
あー！
Ah!
でも 柔らかい 柔らかい...
But it's soft... It's soft...
優しい 優しい？
It's gentle. Gentle?
優しい... 柔らかい...
Gentle... Soft...
これに関してはちょっと ゼタの感覚が狂ってるかもしれない
Regarding this, Zeta's sense of touch might be messed up.
えー！？ なになになに？ 怖んだけど！
Eh?! What is it? What is it? That's scary!
いいのか？ ここで... いいのか？
Is it okay? Right here... Is it okay?
いいのか？ ここで
Is it okay right here?
じゃあ みこ先輩頑張ってね
Well, good luck, Miko-senpai!
出た！ 出た ゴッドハンド！
Here it comes! God Hand is here!
いや これ ゴッドハンドのリアクション来るか？
Is God Hand's reaction coming?
スタート！
Start!
うわあああ！
Uwaaaa!
来た！ ゴッドハンドのリアクション！
Here it is! God Hand's reaction!
いやああ！
Iyaaa!
躊躇っています！
She's hesitating!
手を入れることを躊躇っているが...
She's hesitating to put her hand in...
うえぇ！
Ugh!
なんか... 人の顔じゃないか？！
Isn't it... isn't it a human face?!
いや 人の... ぬるぬるするよな...
Wait, a person's... it feels slimy, right?
食べ物？ いや そんなことはない
Food? No, that can't be...
ちょっとヤバいことが起きてるんじゃないか？
Isn't something really bad happening?!
あの箱の中で... 事件が起きている！
Inside that box... A crime is taking place!
マスクをしてたと思うんだよね だからウチは...
I think it was wearing a mask. So I think...
ピエロのマスクなんじゃないかと思いました
I thought it might be a clown mask.
えーっと 白い... 白塗りの女性の... 顔！
Um, a white... a white-painted woman's... face!
怖ぇよ！ マスク？ マスクか！
That's scary! Mask? A mask!
その答え 怖ぇよ！
That answer is way too scary!
おそらく... YAGOOのカツラ！
Most likely... YAGOO's wig!
絶対カツラだったと思うんだよ！
I'm sure it was a wig!
ロングヘア... ロングヘアYAGOO？
Long hair... Long hair YAGOO?
可能性高そう！
That seems very likely!
名探偵みこ先輩に賭けてみようかな
Maybe I'll trust Detective Miko-senpai.
答えは... ロングヘアYAGOO！
The answer is... Long-hair YAGOO!
あちゃー！ 残念だね！
Uh-oh, too bad!
不正解です！
Wrong answer!
なんか怖いんだけど！
Wait, that's kinda scary!
当たってるー！ あーづちー！
She was right! AZKi~!
当たってるの怖いんだけど！
Getting it right is actually terrifying!
次の者 お願いします！
Next person, please!
じゃあ ゴッドハンドみこちゃんがいってみましょうか
Well then, shall God Hand Miko-chan give it a try?
名探偵 頼むよー
Detective, I'm counting on you!
ゴー！ ゴー！ ゴー！
Go! Go! Go!
ギャアー！
Gyaaah!
待って！ 濡れてる！
Wait! It's wet!
今日一の絶叫出たけど大丈夫？
You just gave your loudest scream of the day, are you okay?
うわあ！
Uwaa!
実況してよ！ 実況！
Describe it! Give us commentary!
なんかチクチクしてて...
It feels prickly...
ぬるぬるしてて... 濡れてて！
It's slimy... and wet!
全部... あの トゲトゲがあります！
Everything... um, has spikes on it!
全んにトゲトゲがある？ いっぱいいる！
It has spikes everywhere? There are lots of them!
トゲトゲした生き物が... いっぱいいるって何？
Spiky creatures... What does "there are lots of them" mean?
いっぱいいる！
There are lots of them!
AZKi先輩のほうがいいかな？
Maybe AZKi-senpai should go?
冷静な判断ができるのか...
Can she make a calm judgment?
AZKi先輩 ゴー！
AZKi-senpai, go!
え？ なに？
Eh? What?
なんか濡れてる... 濡れてる！
It's kind of wet... It's wet!
やっぱり濡れてるんだ！ 湿っています！
It really is wet! It's damp!
湿ってる？ え 何この...
It's damp? Eh, what is this...
トゲトゲした... 球体のような...
Spiky... sphere-like...
球体と その下にもトゲトゲしたものが...
A sphere, and below it there are also spiky things...
痛くはないけど...
It doesn't hurt though...
え これ何だ？
Eh, what is this?
え めっちゃムズいんだ じゃあ
Eh, so it's super difficult then!
何だこれー！ なんか湿ってるー！
What is this?! It's kind of damp!
ミオちゃんですかね 次...
Maybe Mio-chan is next...
なんか嫌だな その感触を聞いた状態で触るのちょっと嫌かも...
I kind of hate this, touching it after hearing about that texture...
ゴー！
Go!
嫌だな... 濡れてるって前情報で嫌だ...
I hate this... Knowing it's wet beforehand makes it worse...
ああ！ やっぱり濡れてるな！
Ah! It really is wet!
濡れてる？
It's wet?
濡れてるけど... なんか硬くて...
It's wet, but... it's kind of hard...
たくさんいる！ たくさんいるぞ！
There are a lot! There are a lot!
一体何なんだよー！
What on earth is it?!
でもあんまり見かけないやつな気がする...
But I feel like it's something you don't see often...
これか？
Is it this?
むずいんじゃない？
Isn't it hard?
え、むずいんだ！ゼタ行こう！
Eh, it's hard! Go Zeta!
行け行け！頑張れゼタ！
Go, go! Do your best, Zeta!
オッケー、オッケー。それでは...
Okay, okay. Well then...
スタート！
Start!
うわー！おおー！
Woah! Oh!
ああ、オッケーオッケー。
Ah, okay, okay.
あ、オッケー？お、早い！
Ah, okay? Oh, so fast!
もしかしてこれさ、我々はあんまり馴染みないけど...
Could it be that we aren't very familiar with this...
ゼタには馴染みあるの？
but Zeta is familiar with it?
もしかしたら、いっぱい触ったことあるかも。
Maybe she's touched it a lot before.
え？馴染み深い？
Huh? Very familiar?
馴染み深いんだよ、ゼタにとって。
It's very familiar for Zeta.
我々にしたらちょっと難しいかも。
It might be a bit difficult for us.
イエーイ！オッケー！
Yay! Okay!
これはね...
As for this...
おそらくこれは... ウニの仲間！
This is probably... a relative of sea urchin!
ウニ？！
Sea urchin?!
AZKiの答えは... 苔！
AZKi's answer is... moss!
ちょっとずついっぱいが生えている感じ...
It feels like lots of tiny things growing...
でも確かに湿ってたしね。
But indeed, it was moist.
うちの答えは... ライチ！
My answer is... lychee!
ライチ？！
Lychee?!
ゼタはね、多分... インドネシアの果物に近いかも。
Zeta thinks, maybe... it's close to an Indonesian fruit.
いっぱいなんかトゲトゲの...
Like lots of spiky...
なんていう食べ物？
What fruit is it called?
名前は、ランブータン！
The name is rambutan!
ランブータン？！
Rambutan?!
でもわかんない、ここにはランブータンはいないのかな？
But I don't know, maybe rambutan isn't around here?
自信持って！
Have confidence!
そうだよ、ゼタが一番分かってたよ！じゃあそれで行きましょうよ！
That's right, Zeta understood it best! Let's go with that then!
答えは、せーの... ランブータン！
The answer is, ready, set... Rambutan!
ピンポーンピンポーン！正解でーす！
Ding ding ding! That is correct!
イエーイ！すごい！
Yay! Amazing!
ちょっと待って、うちライチとか言ってたけど全然違うじゃん！
Wait a second, I said lychee, but it's completely different!
何これー！ライチの味がするかも！
What's this?! It might taste like lychee!
似てる！美味しいよこれ。
They're similar! This tastes good.
初めて見た。
First time seeing it.
甘いの？
Is it sweet?
甘いかも！
It might be sweet!
ちょっと甘っぽい。新しい果物に出会いました。
Kinda sweet-ish. We've encountered a new fruit.
正解の答えも不正解の答えもありましたね。
There seems to have been correct and incorrect answers.
でも......
But...
ゼタ！
Zeta!
どうやらあなたの推理力はまだまだみたいだね？
It seems like your investigative skills are not quite up to par yet.
もっと頑張らないと。
You need to work harder.
つまり、そう......
Or, in other words...
スキルの問題ね！
Skill issue!
見て、スキルが問題のゼタだわ！
Oh, look at her with the skill issues!
あっ、怒っちゃった！
She's getting mad!
あらあら！
Oh dear!
まったく、こんなのも解けないなんて！
Wow, you can't even solve that!
みんな、よくやったわ！
Everyone else, you did great!
次のテストも頑張ってくださいね！
Good luck on the next test!
またね！
See y'all!
えー！ゼタも頑張ったのにー！
What?! Zeta worked hard too!
キャー！何これー？！
Kyaa! What is this?!
さっき笑ったの？！
Did you laugh earlier?!
ちょっと舐めてたね！
You were looking down on her!
笑ってんじゃねーよ！笑うんじゃねーよお前！
Don't laugh! Don't you laugh, you!
一生懸命やったんだぞ！
She worked really hard!
あんまりいじめんなって！かわいそうでしょ！
Don't bully it too much! Poor thing!
AZKi、AZKi！ AZKi優しい。
AZKi, AZKi! AZKi is kind.
もっと床にはいつくばりなさい。
Humble yourself even more on the floor.
AZKiさん？！凄まじい！
AZKi-san?! How harsh!
ありがとうねみんな、来てくれて本当に！
Thank you everyone for coming, really!
誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday!
今日は集めてくれてありがとうね本当に。
Thank you so much for gathering today.
次のテストの時間だから、行ってくるね！
It's time for the next test, so I'll be going!
頑張れー！いってらっしゃい！
Good luck! Take care!
また会いましょうー！バイバーイ！
See you later! Bye-bye!
ゾンビもっと祝いなさいよ！もっとゼタを祝いなさい！
Zombie, celebrate more! Celebrate Zeta more!
Wait, there's like a ring.
Wait, is this like a boxing ring?
Wait, what am I gonna have to do here?
No way. Are we gonna have to fight?
I'm not good at fighting though. I mean I can try!
Happy birthday, Zeta! Long time no see!
This is Amelia Watson,
hololive EN's number one time-traveling detective!
How've you been?
I've been good! How are you?!
Ah, glad to see you're doing well!
Yeah, I prepared the second test,
but we also have other transfer students.
Let's call them in now!
Don't let the first contestant's size fool you!
When you hear her name and her infamous line!
"Small but mighty, always rock hard. I'm rocking in!"
Please welcome... Koseki Bijou!
Koseki Bijou!
Happy birthday, Zeta! Today, I'm rock hard just for you.
Thank you! I'm honored!
Coming to the ring, she's the hero we didn't ask for, but somehow still believe in!
She's everyone's last hope, because all the good ones were busy!
Her line is, "Meet your end, and... despair! Haiyah!"
Oh my god! Look at that walk!
Crashing... Oh my!
Happy birthday, Zeta.
I'm taking you down... down under!
Ladies and gentlemen, hide your dumbbells and protect your ego!
Because this grim reaper doesn't just reap souls, she rips the gym apart!
Her favorite line is, "Only time can out-bench me."
Please welcome... Mori Calliope!
Happy birthday, Zeta! Thank you!
Yeah, boy! Yeah, boy!
Good! Everyone has gathered, right?
This is probably a big surprise, huh?
And I'm sure you're all wondering what kind of test this is gonna be! Anyone have any guesses?
Don't say ground pounding.
Oh, correct!
We're holding a physical test using this long stick with these Bazo weights...
...to determine if you are fit enough to pass off as a secret agent!
Okay, okay. For level 1 of the physical test!
First, lift Bazo from the ring mat up to your hips as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
For level 2, the mat will be bumpy! You'll do the same thing as many times as you can within 30 seconds!
And for the last level, you'll stand on the bumpy mat and balance a cup on your head! Make sure you don't drop it, and lift Bazo up!
Well then, are you guys ready? Let's go!
Okay, who's ready for the physical test?
Okay, maybe we should have Bijou start first?
All right, I got it!
Okay, are you ready? Yeah! Start!
21!
So IRyS...
I'm gonna prove them people wrong! Yes, my full potential!
I'm gonna prove those people wrong! Yes, my full potential!
Start!
Wait, it's a tie! It's a tie!
Oh, you said it's more of a speed thing, isn't it?
Show us... Ready, start!
One! Two! Three!
Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine!
Ten! Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen!
Oh my god! Fourteen!
Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen!
She's locking in! Eighteen!
Nineteen! Twenty! Twenty-one! Twenty-two!
Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Oh my god!
Twenty-five! Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine!
Time's up!
Okay, okay. Anyway, that was...
Look! What's her score? Twenty-nine! Twenty-nine!
Like I said, you have to show us what you're made of.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay...
Okay, you're gonna count down for me? - Of course.
You ready? - Yeah! - All right. Start!
One! Two! Three! Four!
Five! Six! Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten!
Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen!
Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty! Twenty-one!
Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five! Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine!
Thirty! Time's up!
Whoa! - That was awesome! - I can't stand up!
You did great!
Look at the score! Thirty!
She is a secret agent, after all! - That's enough workout for this year.
Yeah!
Okay... Now who's ready for Level 2?
I don't know about this one...
Wait a minute! That's not fair! Those are big pebbles!
That's nothing! - That's not fair!
She has an advantage!
Pebbles, are you seeing this? - Oh god...
Oh, it hurts so... Oh my god! Okay, start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five! Six!
Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten! Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen! Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three! Twenty-four! Twenty-five!
Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine! Thirty!
Time's up!
Whoa! Was that her full power?
The rocks were helping her! - The rocks gave me strength!
When one's running low on acid...
Go on, show the world again. You have to...
Show them who you are! Prove to the world that you are strong!
Take your time. How does it feel?
Tell me when you're ready. Ready? Start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine!
Ten! Eleven! Twelve! Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen!
Sixteen! Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty!
Time's up! You did it!
You don't have to keep standing there! - She's lost for words!
Twenty! - I'm not gonna go that hard, I'm not gonna lie.
It's not like the pebbles are gonna help me. All right, well, I'll try to just do my best.
You got this! Tell me when you're ready!
All right, I'm good. - Okay, start!
One! Two! Three! Four! Five! Six!
Seven! Eight! Nine! Ten! Eleven! Twelve!
Thirteen! Fourteen! Fifteen! Sixteen!
Seventeen! Eighteen! Nineteen! Twenty! Twenty-one! Twenty-two! Twenty-three!
Twenty-four! Twenty-five! Twenty-six! Twenty-seven! Twenty-eight! Twenty-nine!
Thirty! Thirty-one! Thirty-two!
Time's up!
Whoa! You did good! - Oh god, I'm good.
You got more than your first time! Thirty-two! Yeah! Your form was perfect!
How are you holding up?
So the final count is 32!
Woo! I'll take it.
Step on those pebbles like they're what...
Who gives you permission? Yeah, who gives you permission?
Deep step on...
She's going Super Saiyan!
Yabai! Something's coming out of me!
All right, Zeta! Are you ready?
Yeah! Three, two, one, start!
One, two, three...
four, five, six, seven...
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve...
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen...
seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, twenty...
twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four...
twenty-five, twenty-six, twenty-seven...
twenty-eight, twenty-nine, thirty...
thirty-one, thirty-two, thirty-three, thirty-four...
thirty-five, thirty-six, thirty-seven...
Time's up!
Whoa! This is impressive!
Pachi pachi pachi! Yay!
Clap clap clap! Yay!
I'm glad you guys are having fun!
Level 3 of the physical test is gonna be pretty tough, though.
You guys ready?
For Level 3, I've got a little something behind me, which is...
A cup! A cup! Would you like a cup of tea?
Um, maybe later. After lunchtime, oh?
While we are stepping on the bumpy mat, we're also going to be balancing this cup on top of our head like this.
Oh! You'll have to use the mat!
It's a combination of everything! Yeah!
And while lifting as well, of course!
Yeah, it doesn't affect us at all! It doesn't affect...
Okay, crown! Give her the crown! From the princess!
There you go! It's so over! It's so over!
Are you ready? Remember to use your butt and your legs. Form is important. Okay, butt and my legs. Okay, form!
Are you ready? Okay, start!
One, two, three...
four, five, six, seven...
eight, nine, ten...
Oh no! Eleven, twelve...
thirteen, fourteen, fifteen...
sixteen, seventeen, eighteen...
nineteen, twenty...
twenty-one, twenty-two, twenty-three...
twenty-four, twenty-five, twenty-six...
twenty-seven, twenty-eight...
Time's up!
How many was that? I like how the cup was stuck on her head.
Yeah, that was funny. And then it turned over and it was hot on her head! Oh, that was so funny!
28! You got 28!
IRyS, it's IRyS! IRyS, it's Princess IRyS!
Beautiful posture. Yeah, exactly! Show us posture!
This is her strong point because she's so good at keeping it on her head.
Wait a sec, don't put it on me yet! Don't put it on me yet!
Okay, you may place it on my head, the crown! My coronation!
Three, two, one, start!
One, two...
Three, four...
five, six, seven...
eight, nine...
ten, eleven...
twelve...
Time's up!
This stupid cup! This stupid cup! Don't blame the cup, it's not the cup's fault.
Maybe my good form will come in handy here. Yeah, exactly! You may place the tiara on my head.
You have to step on it first. Oh come on... It's the pain before... the gain!
Pain before the gain! Pain is beauty!
All right, all right, let's do it. I shall place it on top of the crown, so you have double crown!
Okay! Are you ready, Dad? Maybe. Okay, maybe!
Three, two, one, start!
One, two, three, four, five...
6! 7! 8! 9! Good posture! 10!
11! 12! Something's dripping! 13! 14! 15! 16! 17!
18! 19! 20! 21! 22! 23! 24! Time's up!
That was my goal! That was my goal!
Yeah, 24! And I didn't lose the cup even once!
Are you sure? Maybe there was tape... I think she cheated!
Eh? Super glue?
Let's really test it! You can use me as the test!
Yeah! It... it doesn't turn!
Happy birthday! Yeah! And you know what?
Directly right in the center of your head, so that it's less likely to fall.
This is like the best birthday ever. Aww! Yay, I'm glad!
Now then, are you ready? 3, 2, 1, start!
1! 2! 3! 4! 5! 6! 7! 8! 9! 10!
11! 12! 13! 14! 15! 16! 17! 18!
19! 20! 21! 22! 23! 24! 25! 26! Time's up!
You did it! 26 is your final number!
Does that mean the scores are what I think it is? I think so!
Is anyone keeping score? Staff-san has been keeping score for us!
Yes! You are a winner! I am! You are the winner!
What are the scores again? What matters is what's inside!
Seems like you guys completed the test! Woohoo!
Some of you were able to lift pretty well. Maybe not for some, though.
It was so much fun just watching! But come on, Zeta! You're the birthday girl!
You should be showing us your crazy skills or something! Prove it to us next test, okay?
Well then, thank you for having me! This is Amelia Watson signing off. Until next time! Bye!
Ame has really high standards, okay? Even if you won...
Thank you so much!
Bye-bye! See ya!
あいつ狙おう！よし！
Let's aim at her! Okay!
うわー！やめろ！背中狙われた！やめて！
Whoa! Stop! You targeted my back! Stop it!
やめてー！死ぬー！容赦ない！
Stop it! I'm gonna die! You're relentless!
容赦なさすぎる！
You're way too relentless!
はいはいはい！楽しそう、楽しそう！
Alright, alright, alright! Looks like fun!
ゼータ！え？何？何で水鉄砲持ってるの？
Zeta! Huh? What? Why do you have water guns?
やめて！やめて！やめて！
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
うわ！持ってるやん！
Whoa! You have one too!
どういうこと？誰か説明して〜！
What's going on? Someone explain~!
Bokobokobo~ Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day! Ehei!
Zeta, happy birthday! ありがとう〜！
Zeta, happy birthday! Thank you~!
I already told them what to do before you came here, so they know the rules!
この水鉄砲で君のエイム力を確かめるよ！
We're gonna be testing your aim skills with this water gun!
In shooting level 1, we will see how many immobile targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
In level 2, we will see how many moving targets you can hit within 30 seconds!
And level 3 will test if you can hit the targets on the moving zombie!
誰が最強のエイム力を持っているかなー？
Who do you think has the best aim skills here?
はい！俺だ！
Me! It's me!
トワたち、みんな何とFPSやってるんだよね！
Towa and the others all play FPS games!
そうだねー！私はやってないけどね！余裕や余裕！
That's right! Though I don't play them! Easy peasy!
頑張ろう！
Let's do our best!
誰が勝つんでしょうかという感じなんですか？
So it's a question of who will win, huh?
負けませんよ
I won't lose!
私も負けないよー
I won't lose either~
Level 1
提らに...
Over here...
動かない標的があるので、こちらをみんなで1人ずつ撃っていこうかなと思います
there are stationary targets, so let's each take turns shooting them.
頑張るー！
I'll do my best!
順番どうしましょう？
How should we decide the turn order?
やりたい！やりたい！
I wanna go! I wanna go!
まつりちゃんは言い出しっぺだし
Since Matsuri-chan suggested it first,
撃たない3人にはね、ここら辺で見てもらいましょう
the three of us who aren't shooting will watch from around here.
はーい
Okay!
3, 2, 1
スタート！
Start!
うま！
So good!
ごめん！
Sorry!
外してなくない？
Isn't she not missing at all?
まつさんがパーフェクト...
Matsu-san is getting a perfect score...
パーフェクトおじさんじゃない？
Isn't she "Perfect Ojisan"?
やば！
Crazy!
うますぎる！
She's way too good!
残り15秒！
15 seconds remaining!
えー！？
Whaaa?!
これみんなには分かんないけど、数字すら見えないこれ
Everyone might not realize, but you can't even see the numbers from here.
すごい！偏差とかもなしに
Amazing! Without even adjusting for lead distance!
え、これ最後？
Wait, is this the last one?
えー？！
Whaaat?!
あと1個！あと1個！
One more! One more!
おー！
Woah!
ノーミス！
Flawless!
え、すごーい！
Woah, amazing!
ノーミス！
Flawless!
まつりちゃん一発も外さずすべて取れました！
Matsuri-chan didn't miss a single shot and got them all!
いやー！
Yay!
うますぎるよね！
She's way too good!
うますぎるよね。なんかちょっと行きづらいわ
She's so good that it's kinda intimidating to go next.
私行く？
Should I go?
お、マジ？
Oh, really?
吾輩でしょ、次。吾輩！
It's my turn next, right? Mine!
あ、トワ様か
Ah, Towa-sama?
じゃあトワ！
Then Towa!
頑張れー！
Do your best!
支える、支える感じで行こう
Let's go with a supporting grip.
じゃあ、カウントするね
Okay, I'll count down!
3, 2, 1
スタート！
Start!
ここ！
Here!
おー！速い！速い！
Ooh! Fast! Fast!
ここ！
Here!
速い！
Fast!
警察だ！はい、警察！
It's the police! Yes, police!
え、え？
Huh, wait what?
うまい、うまい！めっちゃ速い！
Good, good! Extremely fast!
ここ！
Here!
え、うまっ！ここ！
Whoa, skill! Here!
うわあー！
Woah!
だんだん超えてくるんだ、これ
The pressure keeps mounting with each person!
これは...
This is...
次どうする？
What should we do next?
いやー！
Oh no~
先やった方がいい！先やった方がいい！
Better to go sooner! Better to go sooner!
とりあえずね！とりあえずね！
For now, yeah! For now!
下半身作戦！下半身作戦！
Lower body tactic! Lower body tactic!
下半身を安定させる！ぶれないようにする！
Stabilize the lower body so you don't sway!
ポーズダッセぇ！
That pose looks so lame!
ダサすぎる！これで行くから！
Way too lame! But I'm going with this!
3, 2, 1, どうぞ！
3, 2, 1, go ahead!
ほら！
Look!
頑張れー！
Do your best!
頑張れ！
安定させて！
Keep it stable!
あ、いいよいいよ！当たってる！
Ah, good, good! It's hitting!
適当に撃ってる！
She's just shooting blindly!
あ、でも惜しい惜しい！
Ah, but close, close!
空に...空に撃ってる！
Into the... She's shooting into the sky!
もっと上！もっと上！
Higher! Higher!
頑張れ！頑張れ！あ、それ空だぞ！
Do your best! Do your best! Ah, that's the sky!
ラプラスの結果は...まあ、2個だな
Laplus's result is... well, 2 targets.
イェーイ！
Yay!
最後、行きますか！
Shall we go with the last one?
行けー！頑張れー！
Go for it! Do your best!
ということで、じゃあ最後ゼータ。打ち合わせね
So for the last one, Zeta. We had a strategy meeting,
1秒で、1秒で
in 1 second, in 1 second!
いやいやいや
No, no, no, no!
準備OK？ 準備OK！
Are you ready? Ready!
行くよ！ 3, 2, 1, Go!
Here we go! 3, 2, 1, Go!
うわー！上手い上手い！
Whoa! So good, so good!
うまい！
Good!
3個目？上手い！
Third one? So good!
思ってたより上手い！
Better than expected!
上手いやん！
You're good!
いや、これは...
Whoa, this is...
ごめん
Sorry!
全然余裕余裕！
Plenty of time, plenty of time!
行けた！あ、ちょっと待って！
Got it! Ah, wait a second!
どこだ？
Where is it?
右、右、そこら辺！
Right, right, around there!
下！下！下！
Down! Down! Down!
どこにある？ どこだ？
Where is it? Where?
あれ？
Huh?
画面外だ！
It's off-screen!
残った！
It stayed!
すごい！神様が手伝ってくれた
Amazing! A god helped her out!
まいっか！
Oh well!
まつり先輩ナイスショット！
[Matsuri-senpai, nice shot!]
なんかギリギリ滑り込みで、半端ないって！
That was barely in time, insane!
イェーイ！
Yay!
Level 2
あちらをご覧ください！
Please look over there!
はい！ 動いてる！
Yes! They're moving!
動いてる！むちゃくちゃ！
They're moving! That's insane!
はい、頑張っていきましょう！
Alright, let's do our best!
じゃあ、誰から行く？
So who's going first?
俺だ俺だ俺だ！
Me, me, me!
我輩が行きたい！
I wanna go!
もう行っちゃったから、じゃあラプラスからね
She already stepped up, so starting with Laplus then.
やったもん勝ちでヤバい
Stepping up first to get it over with is crazy.
では行きましょう！ラプラス、いきますよ！
Then let's go! Laplus, here I go!
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, start!
このゲームには必勝法がある
There's a guaranteed winning strategy in this game.
めっちゃ回っとるやん！
You're spinning like crazy!
うわー！
Uwah!
ねぇ、これズルい！
Hey, this is cheating!
後ろから撃ってるのヤバいって！
Shooting from behind is insane!
当たってないよ！
They're not hitting!
当たってない！見て！
They're not hitting! Look!
当たってないよ！
They're not hitting!
腕、腕、腕、腕！
Arm, arm, arm, arm!
ぐるんぐるんだから、カメラ！
The camera is spinning around!
キミ、あと5秒しかないよ！
Hey, you only have 5 seconds left!
1個しか倒せてないよ！
You've only hit one!
ヤバい！頑張れ！
Oh no! Do your best!
あ、でも1個... いいよ1個！
Ah, but you hit one, one is good!
1個？あの、後ろ向きでね...
At least one? With your back turned...
絶対行きたい！
I definitely want to go!
絶対行きたい？行きたい、行きたい！
You definitely want to go? I do, I do!
はい、じゃあござる行ってみましょう！
Okay, let's go with Gozaru!
行ってみましょう！
Let me do this!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ラプラスみたいに後ろ向かなくていい？
Do I not need to face away like Laplus?
ううん、大丈夫！
Nope, you're fine!
それでは挑戦、行ってみましょう！
Now then, let's begin the challenge!
3、2、1... スタート！
3, 2, 1... Start!
これ... 頑張れ！
Do your best!
当たってない！難し！
I'm not hitting them! So hard!
難しい！むずい！
It's hard! So hard!
いや、回ってるんだけど、私が...
No, I'm the one who's spinning...
回ってる、回ってる！
You are spinning, you are spinning!
回ってる！
Spinning!
あ、当たった！当たった！
Ah, you hit it! You hit it!
あ、裏面だったな...
Ah, that was the back side...
裏面だったな...
It was the back side...
ヤバい！
Oh no!
後ろ、後ろ！
Behind, behind!
これはもう後ろから...
This is already from behind...
画面から...
From the screen...
いや、惜しかった！
Ah, that was close!
残念！0達成、0枚です！
Too bad! 0 targets hit!
むちゃくちゃ... これむずいよ！
That's insane... This is so hard!
いや、でも惜しかったのあったね！
But there were some close ones!
裏がヤバい！裏が！
The back is crazy! The back!
裏面だったからすごい...！
Because it was the back side...
最後イヤだから、まつり行かせてください！
I don't want to go last, so let Matsuri go next!
行っちゃった、行っちゃった！
She already went, she already went!
行っちゃった！
She went!
まつり先輩！
Matsuri-senpai!
行くぞー！3、2、1、ゴー！
Here I go! 3, 2, 1, Go!
行けー！
Go!
お、上手！上手い、上手い！マジ？
Oh, good! Nice, nice! Really?
あ、惜しい！
Ah, close!
ダメなんだ... お！
It didn't count... Oh!
おー！上手い！すごい！
Ooh! So good! Amazing!
あ、今のところ最高だよ、これ！
Ah, this is the best score so far!
そうだよね！2個の時点でね！
Right! Getting 2 targets!
むずいんだから、これ！
Since this is so hard!
狙ってるうちにどんどん時間が過ぎてく！
While aiming, time keeps ticking away!
これ後ろじゃない、後ろじゃない！
This isn't behind, isn't behind!
後ろ！
Behind!
後ろはね...
The back side is...
ヤバい！ヤバいです！
Oh no! This is bad!
ヤバいのではありません！
It's not bad!
100... 2個か！
100... 2 targets, huh!
いや、でも最高だよね！1位だよね！
No, but that's the highest! You're 1st place!
なんかこれ気付いたぞ、トワちゃん。
I noticed something about this, Towa-chan.
うん、追わない方がいい。絶対そう！
Yeah, better not to chase them. Definitely!
トワも思ってた！一点集中！
Towa thought so too! Focus on one spot!
一点集中で、きたとこパーンの方が...
Focus on one spot and shoot when it passes...
アドバイスを活かして、やろうかな！
I'll try using that advice!
イエーイ！
Yay!
トワちゃんの挑戦！3、2、1、ゴー！
Towa-chan's turn! 3, 2, 1, Go!
頑張れ！行けー！
Do your best! Go!
ほい！おー！惜しい！
Hop! Woah! So close!
やば、こっち向け！やばい！
Oh no, face this way! Oh no!
うわー！え、え、え！
Woah! What, what, what?!
あ、裏だ！
Ah, it's the back side!
裏... うわー！
Back... Woah!
頑張れー！
Do your best!
うわ、行けた行けた！あと10秒！
Woah, nice nice! 10 seconds left!
はい！頑張れ！
Yes! Do your best!
タイミング、タイミングだ！
Timing, it's all about timing!
おー！おー！全部裏面！
Woah! Woah! They're all the back side!
3、2、1... ヤバい！
3, 2, 1... Oh no!
いや、これむずいよー！
No, this is so hard!
え、これクソむずいじゃん！1枚でした！
What, this is freaking hard! I got 1 target!
一緒だ、ござると！
Tied with Gozaru!
申し訳ないけど後ろの人と一緒。
Sorry, but I'm tied with the person behind me.
ホントに...
Really...
[Level 3]
普通の標的、動く標的ときて、なんとこちら！ポン！
After normal targets and moving targets, look at this! Bam!
うわー！ゾンビ！
Woah! A zombie!
きもい、きもい！怖いよ！
Gross, gross! So scary!
ゾンビの動く標的になってます！
It's a moving zombie target!
でも標的自体は2つしかないから！確かに！
But there are only two targets on it! True!
こちらを狙って... なんか気持ち悪いポーズもしてますけど...
Aim for these... though it's making weird poses...
こいつ自我があるぞ！自我が！
This guy has a mind of its own! A mind!
トワちゃんから、じゃあ行きましょう！
Starting with Towa-chan, let's go!
3、2、1、ゴー！
3, 2, 1, Go!
え、なんか... うわ！
Wait, what... Woah!
え、ごめん！イージー、イージー！
Wait, sorry! Easy, easy!
あ、でもなんか... おい！おい！こっち向け！こっち向け！
Ah, but wait... Hey! Hey! Look over here! Look over here!
やばい！いや、ちょっと待って！
Oh no! No, wait a second!
待って、やばい、やばい！
Wait, oh no, oh no!
頭の... 頭の... 変わるんだ！
On its head... its head... It changes!
やばい！おい！
Oh no! Hey!
でも... キモいポーズだ！
But... what a gross pose!
頑張れ！
Do your best!
よし！クリア！
Alright! Clear!
え、ギリギリだったん... 2つちゃんと割れました！ありがとうございます！
Eh, that was close... both cracked properly! Thank you!
なんかゾンビがたまに自我を持ち始めて不思議な動きをするので皆さま注意を
Sometimes the zombie starts having a mind of its own and makes strange moves, so please be careful everyone.
行きたい、行きたい！じゃあ、まつりちゃんね！
I want to go, I want to go! Okay, Matsuri-chan then!
頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best!
夏色まつりちゃん！
Natsuiro Matsuri-chan!
はい！3、2、1、どうぞ！
Okay! 3, 2, 1, go ahead!
早っ！速い、速い、速い！
So fast! Fast, fast, fast!
え！え！
What! What!
はやっ！
So fast!
3秒で終わりました！
It ended in 3 seconds!
3秒！
3 seconds!
ダメー！
Nooo!
落ち込んでるよ！
He's getting depressed!
やっちゃった、やっちゃった！
I did it, I did it!
今まつりちゃんが3秒で撃ち抜いちゃったということは
Now that Matsuri-chan shot it down in 3 seconds,
たぶんもう次のゾンビは「この動きしちゃいけないな」って風になって...
the next zombie will probably learn, "I shouldn't move like this"...
やばい、学習するタイプだ！
Oh no, it's the type that learns!
学習ゾンビなんだ！
It's a learning zombie!
ちょっと待って、じゃあ先やる？
Wait a sec, should I go first?
先にやる！先にやる！
I'll go first! I'll go first!
でもさ、主役が最後でしょ！
But the star is supposed to go last!
3, 2, 1, スタート！
3, 2, 1, Start!
当たるんかい！
It hits, really?!
なんで当たるんだよ！
Why is it hitting?!
頭抜けるよね！
Its head dodges it!
撃ちなさい！
Shoot it!
当たりそう！当たりそう！
It's about to hit!
あと5秒ね！
5 seconds left!
やばい、途中我慢できなかった！
Oh no, I couldn't hold back halfway through!
むかつきすぎて！
Because it was so annoying!
最後の挑戦者はゼータ！ 3, 2, 1, スタート！
The final challenger is Zeta! 3, 2, 1, Start!
めっちゃ動いてる！
It's moving so much!
めっちゃ動いてるよ！
It's really moving!
助けて！
Help me!
すごかった！本当！
That was amazing! Truly!
めちゃめちゃ軽い動きだった！
Her movement was so nimble!
2ポイントです！ わー！ すごーい！
That's 2 points! Woah! Amazing!
みんなー！ このテストで一番ポイントを取ったのは誰か、見てみようか？！
Guys! Should we see who got the most points in this test?!
おー！
Woah!
めっちゃいい勝負！
It's such a close match!
え、まつりが12点。
Matsuri has 12 points.
で、トワちゃんが11点。
And Towa-chan has 11 points.
で、ゼータが10点。
And Zeta has 10 points.
そしてラプラスが 4点！
And La+ has 4 points!
4点！ 4点！
4 points! 4 points!
ラプラスが最下位！
La+ is in last place!
1位までは1位の方へ選んでよ！
Pick the one who came in 1st place!
すごーい！おめでとー！
Wooow! Congrats!
みんなほんとによく頑張ったね！
You guys did very well!
でも何より、みんなが楽しんでくれて嬉しかった。
And best of all, I'm glad everyone had fun.
これからもっとエイム力を上げて、こぼみたいにうまくなれるといいね。
I can't wait to see how much more you can improve your aiming skills in the future, like me.
おい！
Oi.
ちょっと......こっちが喋ってるんだけど？
Um, I'm... I'm talking here.
おい！ こぼの話を聞いてよ！
Oi! Listen to Kobo!
ま、とにかくゼータ！ シークレット・エージェントになれるまで まだまだ遠〜い道のりだよ？いい？
Anyway, Zeta! You still have a long, long way to go to become a full-fledged secret agent, okay?
うん、勝負しょっ！
Yeah, let's have a match one day!
バーイ！またね〜
Bye! See ya~
まだ勝負ついてないよ！
It's not over yet!
こぼからね！逃げた！逃げた！
From Kobo! She ran away! She ran away!
That was such a crazy... I got wet! Look at that, from the water gun!
They were shooting at me like crazy. I even had to change my clothes.
But I heard there's gonna be announcements today. So are you guys ready for the announcements?
A little ad break, yes?
では、告知です！ お願いします！
Now then, here is an announcement! Please!
じゃじゃーん！ うわー、水着！
Tada! Woah, swimsuit!
She's shining, she's shining so bright!
Oh my god! Zeta in an angel-like outfit! Isn't that so cute?
Angel costume! You guys have always said that you're scared of me, so...
...you can't be scared of me now, cause...
...I'm the most seiso person there is! So...
清楚ゼータ！ 清楚ゼータ来た！
Seiso Zeta! Seiso Zeta is here!
どう？ かわいい？
How is it? Cute?
かわいいんでしょう？ 真白だし。
It's cute, right? It's pure white.
The costume looks so cute, right?
Beli berapa kan, guys? Karena kapan lagi bisa lihat Seiso Zeta ya, guys, ya?
How many will you buy, guys? Because when else can you see Seiso Zeta, guys?
Berkostum, berkosplay sebagai angel-angel gitu. Lucu! Iya, iya, Zeta lucu, lucu.
Dressed up, cosplaying as an angel like that. Cute! Yes, yes, Zeta is so cute.
Aku mau! Siapa yang mau? Aku! Aku!
I want it! Who wants it? Me! Me!
But we don't stop here, because...
...obviously, there's gonna be so many more items and we're gonna introduce them now.
じゃ、こちらをご覧ください！ どうぞ！
Now then, please take a look at this! Go ahead!
じゃじゃーん！
Tada!
I'm bad at counting, but that's probably six, right? Isn't that so awesome?!
That's so cool!
So we have acrylic diorama...
...which you can put on your table. Later we'll explain.
And then we have a cap. No cap, okay.
We have a plushie, ぬいぐるみ!
We have a plushie, a plushie!
And not only that, there will of course be Voice...
Sorry, why did I say Voice? There will be Voice Pack...
...and also bonus card as well!
Who wants bonus cards? Me!
So I bet you guys are interested in this! Yeah, definitely!
Kalau kalian tertarik bakal ada 6 item ya guys,
If you're interested, there will be 6 items guys:
acrylic diorama, haori, kucing... eh, kucing...
acrylic diorama, haori, cat... I mean, cat...
Ada topi, ada juga boneka...
There's a cap, there's also a plushie...
いっぱいありますよね。
There are a lot, right?
Bonus card, this is also bonus card, so yeah!
Definitely, um, we're gonna get into it, but stay, stay there.
We're not, we're not done yet. We're not done yet.
はい、次どうぞ！
Okay, next please!
じゃじゃーん！
Tada!
This is my acrylic diorama!
So cute! あるてらママ先生、
So cute! Arutera Mama-sensei,
Thank you so much, sensei!
ママありがとう！
Mama, thank you!
Mama's drawing is always so cute! 可愛いでしょうね。
Mama's drawing is always so cute! It's cute, right?
可愛い。
Cute.
じっと飛んでるよ。
It's floating silently.
凄くない？
Isn't it amazing?
It's super duper cute!
I'm having an... I was, I almost said allergic reaction.
I am having...
...you know that cuteness aggression? Yeah.
That's what I'm feeling. It's so cute!
Okay!
Of course we're gonna, um, go to the next one. There's so much more.
じゃ、次どうぞ！
Well, next please!
じゃじゃーん！
Tada!
なんだと？！羽織？！
What?! Haori?!
Vestia Zeta Haori!
I know that you guys would love to wear this at, like, events,
or like concerts, or maybe, you know, for...
...for future Fes, uh, next Fes. I mean...
You guys can wear it together! You can, like...
...huddle up, wear the same Haori,
and it would be so cute, right?
I mean, I'm wearing a uniform, so you guys can be...
...this can be your uniform.
ライブの時とか、
During concerts and such,
そう、可愛いでしょう？
yeah, it's cute, right?
Like if everyone like wears it together, it's gonna be so cute.
Lucu banget guys, Haori.
It's super cute guys, Haori.
Aku nggak tahu mau ngomong apa, pokoknya ini keren banget!
I don't know what to say, basically this is super cool!
Karena desainnya tuh pertama simpel, terus belakangnya tuh kelihatan Zeta.
Because first, the design is simple, then the back looks like Zeta.
Terus... nggak norak gitu loh guys!
Also... it's not tacky at all, guys!
Kayak keren aja, kayak simpel, keren, cool.
Like it's just cool, simple, sleek, cool.
Jadi kalian juga pakainya bisa
So when you wear it, you can go
ke mana aja, nggak harus kayak konser-konser doang.
anywhere, it doesn't have to be just for concerts.
You can like wear this like outside of concerts as well, cause like it's like a sophisticated...
...a cool looking, like, toned-down Haori, you know?
Befitting for me, the coolest secret agent. Okay, anyways!
There's more! There's more! 次の...
There's more! There's more! Next...
じゃじゃーん！
Tada!
じゃじゃーん！ Wow, uwee...
Tada! Wow, uwee...
Uwee cap! I almost choked on myself.
It's so good!
It's a baseball cap! It's so cool.
You can use this to shield yourself from the sun,
like I do, because I hate the sun.
There's like uwee written on top of the cap.
「うぇぇ」書いてるよ。
It says "Uwee".
そうそうそう、ゼタのセリフ「うぇぇ」って書いてる。
Yeah yeah yeah, Zeta's catchphrase "Uwee" is written on it.
可愛いでしょう？
Isn't it cute?
Of course, there's like my neko... ah, not neko...
Of course, there's like my cat... ah, not cat...
...my hair buns,
coffin Zeta? There's my hair buns there,
and my ribbon. I would call this ribbon. Ignore the whiskers, but...
...if you can ignore the whiskers, those are not cat whiskers.
But it's cute! You can wear it!
A cap! Buy this cap!
It's a good cap. No cap. Hahaha!
It's so cute! Topi ya guys!
It's so cute! It's a cap guys!
Apalagi panas-panas,
Especially when it's hot,
harus pakai topi enggak sih guys? Panas-panas.
you gotta wear a cap, right guys? When it's hot out.
Apalagi silau gitu,
Especially when it's glaring,
keren kalau pakai topi loh, guys.
it looks cool if you wear a cap, guys.
Terus keren lagi, hitam gitu topinya. Keren keren keren.
Plus it's cool that the cap is black like that. Cool, cool, cool.
まだあるのかな？あると思う。
Is there still more? I think there is.
じゃ、次どうぞ！
Well, next please!
Ah... I...
...it's like, it's so cute!
It's a plushie with a cat headband.
It's called the Sleepy Cat Zzz Plushie.
I get that it looks like a cat, I know, but I swear it's not, okay? It's not.
If you notice, it's based on like Cat Day KV, so it's so cute, right?
みんな、あの、Cat Dayのとき覚えてる？
Everyone, do you remember back on Cat Day?
これ、This is the goods from last time.
This is the merch from last time.
It's so cute, right? Look at those eyes! It's so cute!
I want to squish it and... just jumble it up. It's so cute!
And she's like sleeping because, um, I heard that cats nap for 16 hours...
...although that has nothing to do with me, I'm just saying. It's very cute! It's like sleeping.
眠そう。眠そう Zeta-chan. 眠い Zeta-chan. かわいい！
She looks sleepy. Sleepy Zeta-chan. So cute!
Buy it or else! Or else, you don't want to miss this because...
...everyone liked the Cat Day KV, you won't miss this, okay?
Even more, let's see. Next, please! 次、お願いします！
Even more, let's see. Next, please! Next, please!
ボイス！わー！ボイス！
Voice! Wow! Voice!
Voice! And it's titled "A Fateful Meeting".
Last but not least, there's also a bonus for who purchases the full set!
Last but not least, there's also a bonus for whoever purchases the full set!
フルセットを買った人がボーナスをもらえるぞ！
People who buy the full set get a bonus!
Kalian dapat bonus kalau kalian beli full set, okay?
You get a bonus if you buy the full set, okay?
じゃあ、Last one, please! 最後、お願いします！
Well then, last one, please! Last one, please!
じゃジャン！Here's the bonus!
Ta-da! Here's the bonus!
It's a limited edition! You'll get my signature, okay?
It's so good! It's like handwritten signature and all that...
It's so good! It's like a handwritten signature and all that...
It's the best! It's limited, so get it now! Limited...
スペシャルだよね。一番、うん、スペシャル。
It's special, right? Absolutely, yeah, special.
Of course, um, it's a little ad break, but we're not going to stop there because...
...even though it's my birthday, I want to give a gift to you instead, yeah!
But it's not over yet! これで終わりじゃないよ！
But it's not over yet! It's not over yet!
It's my birthday, but I also want to give you a present as well, so...
...are you excited? Okay, let's go get your present!
goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない 熱身任せて
Can't be stopped, surrender to this passion
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down
我慢出来ない Let me free
I can't stand it, let me free
目が眩んでしまいそうな 出で立ちのマーメイド
A mermaid so dazzling she'd blind your eyes
憧れてたっけ But then 今は何も響かない
I used to admire her, but then, now nothing resonates
I know who I am, I
『ブランディング』にはあっかんべー
Sticking my tongue out at "branding"
今は完全無視よ 何でもアリの Greedy style
Ignoring it completely now, anything goes in my greedy style
ダサいやっかみも興味無いの
Not interested in lame jealousy either
ありのままでいたい
I just want to stay as I am
goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない 熱身任せて
Can't be stopped, surrender to this passion
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down
我慢出来ない Let me free
I can't stand it, let me free
We are special でしょ？ 揺るがない Pride
We are special, right? Unshakable pride
それだけでいいの
That's all I need
たらればだらけの Lowな日々を Break it down, break it
Break down these low days full of "what ifs", break it
We are special でしょ？ 誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
We are special, right? No matter what anyone says, I will sing
アンフェアばかりのセカイなど Break it down, break it ススメ
A world full of unfairness, break it down, break it, charge forward
Break it down, break it ススメ
Break it down, break it, charge forward
I just don't care about you!
ハイテクなメイクやファッションも
High-tech makeup and fashion too
Self-loveには敵わないよ
Can't compete with self-love
この身と心 誰の物でも無いでしょ
This body and heart don't belong to anyone, right?
いい加減いい大人だよね...？
I'm well and truly an adult by now, right...?
Ini lah aku apa adanya, tidak sempurna, tapi sepenuhnya diriku
This is who I am, not perfect, but fully myself
でも今は楽しいよ ありのままでいられるから！
But now it's fun, because I can just be myself!
goin' goin' my way もう ほっといて
Goin' goin' my way, just leave me alone
止められない 熱身任せて
Can't be stopped, surrender to this passion
こりごりだ Ruleは Break it down
I'm sick of rules, break it down
我慢出来ない Let me free
I can't stand it, let me free
We are special でしょ？ 揺るがない Pride
We are special, right? Unshakable pride
それだけでいいの
That's all I need
たらればだらけの Lowな日々を Break it down, break it
Break down these low days full of "what ifs", break it
We are special でしょ？ 誰に言われても 私は歌うよ
We are special, right? No matter what anyone says, I will sing
あーもう嫌
Ah, I'm sick of it,
案ばかりの世界
a world full of empty plans.
なら Break it down Break it smash
So break it down, break it smash!
Can break me down Breaking me
Break it down Break it down
Let's go Break it down Break it smash
Goin' goin' my way
もう放っといて
Just leave me alone,
止められない
you can't stop me.
Let me 任せて
Let me handle this!
こりごりだ Rule は
I'm sick and tired of these rules,
Break it down
我慢できない
I can't take it anymore,
Let me free
Thank you, everyone!
That was Break It Down!
飼育員さん If you liked it, make some noise!
Secretaries, if you liked it, make some noise!
MISSION COMPLETE!
[On-Screen Text] MISSION COMPLETE!
MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, SECRETARY!
[On-Screen Text] MY WORLD WOULD NOT BE COMPLETE WITHOUT U, SECRETARY!
YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! ;D
[On-Screen Text] YOUR SUPPORT MEANS THE WORLD TO ME! ;D
LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...!
[On-Screen Text] LET'S KEEP DOING MISSIONS TOGETHER, FOREVER...!
KEEP BREAKIN' IT DOWN!
[On-Screen Text] KEEP BREAKIN' IT DOWN!